Well, we are now live here.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
Shall we go?
Okay, we're going to start recording.
Coming up on the block.
Five minutes, four, three.
Someone who went to Ebitu Chan's spring tour...
I got a lot of letters from people who went to Ebichu's spring tour.
Peoples Tokyo, Yokohama, or Kanagawa...
There are a lot of people who live in the Kanto region
Chasing after EBICHU.
And if that's all there is to it, that's enough.
If that's all there is to it
and send us pictures of the delicious food
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ramen noodles from where?
Ramen noodles. Wait a minute.
I'm going there to eat ramen.
Of course you shouldn't go there just for the food.
What if there was such a guy?
What was it like for you, Mariko?
I feel like I've already done about 10 shows.
I've only done about 4 shows.
I see.
We still have about 15 more shows to go until summer.
So there's still a lot to go?
Yes, there is.
So you have a lot to do until about July?
During July?
No, no, no, but it's amazing.
Everyone's, uh...
Excuse me.
The delivery guy must be a little surprised.
Hello.
Where's Ria Nakajima?
She's absent today.
Oh, hello.
Shingo Kawasaki will be taking her place.
Shingo Kawasaki will be taking your place.
What?
You don't mean you're quitting or something?
No, no, I don't think so.
No! Something like that.
As long as it's not happening on my watch.
I think it's fine.
I think... the way he reacts...
Like, "Oh, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it!
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're watching well, aren't you?
I've seen it all before my very eyes.
Well, today... we have a regular guest who substitutes for a regular guest.
Shingo Kawasaki.
Please.
No, no, no, no, no.
By the way, just now...
Yes, sir.
I'm lucky.
It's called "Cat's Forehead Wide".
It's also known as "Nekohaku".
It's a popular program.
And it's on there.
Yes.
I've been appearing on Tuesdays.
And it's quite a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence at all... the audition process was completely different.
Nakajima Raiya and Shingo Kawasaki are each now regulars at TVK.
That's right.
That's amazing.
Please emphasize that this was just a coincidence.
It's not a barter for something else, right?
Yes, it's just a coincidence.
Well, well, well. That's great!
Well, anyway, I just wanted to say, as a greeting to those who are watching the live broadcast, that he's a great dancer.
He's a great dancer. Then, why don't you say so?
That kind of thing?
I don't know much about dancing, but...
It's just... it's not very sharp.
It's all down.
Yes, yes...
It's like...
What are you doing?
No, no, no. You're surprised.
Oh, you're surprised.
What's with the snap?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, by the way, if you don't mind, just for the record, just for the record.
Verse one, verse two.
Verse one, verse two?
What is it?
Is there a genre?
I've done most of them.
I've done all genres.
I've done all genres, but I'm more into what's called pop, or playing with a little bit of muscle, or
It's cool.
And then there's animation, which is often like this.
I'm good at putting these together
I'm good at doing things like this.
Cool!
What's that?
Punching the muscles.
The sound is amazing!
It's like...
That's how I feel.
But when I'm doing it, I'm saying
"Pan-pan" in my mind when I'm doing it.
Say it.
It's amazing.
Dancing is so powerful when you see it live, isn't it?
I can feel the wind in my hair.
Did it come?
Yeah, I kind of like it.
I'm so happy.
So this week, Shingo Kawasaki...
Shingo Kawasaki is a substitute worker.
He's a regular customer.
This gold devil...
Nakajima Raiya, too.
Sarpon...
He has a Devil name.
What a surprise...
He also has a Devil name.
I gave him a Devil name.
And Mariko became his godmother and gave him that name, too.
Wait, that's a lot of doors.
Four letters, right?
Mo?
It's Mona Lisa.
It's hard to tell, but it's Xavier.
Which one did you start with? Xavier and Mona Lisa are a little bit alike.
The four letters.
Mona Lisa.
What a surprise. His Devil's name is Mona Lisa.
It's a bit confusing, isn't it?
It doesn't look like Mona Lisa at a glance.
But I think that's a good thing.
It's easy to remember.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, without further ado, let's get started.
I've received a lot of letters this week.
So, as I was saying to Mariko earlier...
I just talked with Mariko and she told me that she went to Ebi Choo's tour and ate a lot of things.
There were a lot of them.
Heh...
Well, you're going all over the country, aren't you, and there's delicious food in each place.
I'm so envious that everyone is eating local delicacies.
I'm so envious that you all are eating local delicacies.
First of all, what do you call this?
First of all, what should we do?
You want to take as beautiful a picture as possible, don't you?
Like ramen noodles, of course.
Of course, you take pictures of the food you eat, but...
But when you take a beautiful picture of a landscape, it makes you happy, doesn't it?
There's an amazing guy.
He only takes pictures of sunsets.
Mr. Pell from Hirohoku Ward, Yokohama City
Thank you very much.
I'll just say it's a sunset picture.
I've been so busy lately that I haven't been able to do much sunset hunting.
I enjoy looking at them every day.
The people who aim for sunsets are sunset hunters, aren't they?
So you're a sunset hunter, then.
Okay? First of all...
It looks like this.
Oh, sunset hunters.
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful at this time of night.
It's got a nice gradient.
It's the best.
It's the best of both worlds.
And this one...
Like this.
There's more.
A little help?
Let's see...
I'm Mr. Kuperu.
It's amazing.
I took a picture of this beautiful scaly cloud.
I'm a master.
The daylight hours are getting longer.
It's finally summer, and this is what it looks like.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Beautiful
This is probably in the evening too.
Yes, it is.
This one seems to be all that, too.
This one's on a cell phone.
I see.
You can take such beautiful pictures with a cell phone.
Modern cell phones are amazing.
Scenery?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Now, which one do you want to go to?
There's so much more.
Food...
Let's go.
Let's try the food.
Let's see...
This is... that very thing.
The other day...
The other day, when the three of us went on location to Odawara Hakko...
Seafood... it's right on Sagami Bay...
It's like a roadside station that serves great seafood.
We ate a lot of food there.
That's why you went there.
Yes.
It's called Totoko.
I think "Toto" means "fish" in Japanese.
At a place called Totoko.
I had a kaisendon (a bowl of rice topped with seafood).
Wow!
It's delicious!
Looks so good!
When I was on location.
When I was on location, I had a ramen called Uni Uni Paradise
There was a ramen called "Uni Uni Paradise" that was filled with sea urchin.
You can't even see the noodles because they are covered with sea urchin!
But the price was like 5,000 yen.
That's right.
If it contains that much sea urchin...
That was amazing.
I was curious.
I see.
Sea urchin paradise.
It was delicious.
Really?
What is it?
It was like a thicker version of miso ramen.
Looks delicious!
And this...
You know...
Hyogo Prefecture
There's a famous castle called Himeji Castle
There is a famous castle
There is a white castle there.
I heard that there was a festival held at Himeji Castle, and the normally pure white castle was lit up at night, and it was very beautiful.
It was lit up at night in the color of black clouds.
The color of my guess!
Amazing!
Even the reflections are beautiful!
Does this mean that Himeji Castle is promoting Kurokumo?
It doesn't glow light blue.
Hey...
You should say that.
You should say it out loud.
You don't want me to show it to him?
What's Himeji Castle doing?
That's the scariest thing I've ever heard you say.
Like, "Heh.
No, but...
It's amazing.
Himeji Castle.
It's a national treasure.
Yes, yes, yes...
It's a little...
It's a little different.
Yes?
You don't mind snakes, do you?
I don't find them creepy.
I don't mean creepy... or scary.
It's like...
I'm afraid of the preamble.
Some people don't like that kind of thing.
I'm fine with it.
Let's see...
Special Mission Specialist Catnip Unyia.
Yokohama New Comprehensive Area
Yes, sir.
Master Admiral.
Mona Lisa
Ebiichu no kawaii byte-chan
Yes, sir
It's called "Konnban Devil," sir.
Eh?
The other day, in the river near where this person lives
a snake was swimming comfortably
So, this is the reason why
It looks like an albino of a striped snake
It looks like a golden color and the temperature seems to rise
I hope it will go up.
Inside the water
It's amazing!
By the way, snakes are very good in the water. Wow! There's a snake!
By the way, snakes are really good underwater.
Is that so?
Well, they're fast, and they use this body first.
You know how swimmers often swim like this?
Yes, yes.
Snakes are specialists at that.
Ah...
By undulating their body like this...
By undulating their body like this, they go very fast.
And only here...
Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew.
Like a submarine.
Can you do that too?
Yes, it works. It's really fast.
Maybe it's better in water.
That's true.
The snake is probably...
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you mean?
What? The snake is yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
You didn't give me any reaction.
No, no, no. I was about to say...
I was going to say, "Why do you have balls on your head?
Snake, yes, yes, yes, yes...
Shut up!
I remember now.
Son of a bitch!
Why is it stalling a bit? It's like he's been in water.
Oh, and by the way, this panda in distress...
He drew a picture of a memorable scene that happened that week.
He's very good.
I mean, it's adorable.
He has a very good eye for detail.
I think about this from time to time.
Just in time...
Soon...
There was a popular detective drama series called "Dangerous Deka," starring Kyohei Shibata and Hiroshi Tachi, set in Yokohama.
I know it.
I know the movie.
My brother loves it. He's been watching it since he was little.
He's going to the event, too.
I see.
So that's how much you like it.
It was really popular at the time, and I was watching it in Tokyo at the time, but Yokohama is such a fashionable town, and they frequently filmed around there.
It was almost all Yokohama. It was really in the area. So, when the topic came up, I was just about to shift to the bedrock, and I thought, "Well, isn't Emma the bedrock?
Then it was Emma, wasn't it?
My first name is Eiji, isn't it?
It's just like Taka and Yuji.
I see.
Emma and Eiji are dangerous idiots.
That's the scariest.
How scary!
They're like dangerous idiots.
He's so cute!
Dangerous idiots!
Scariest, but scarier than a dangerous idiot.
What are we doing?
Come on, Emma! Emma! Emma! Emma, let's go! It's like...
I'm scared.
It's the other way around.
Only the master is scary. And it's the other way around. That's right.
Only the master.
Yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There are also things like this. You are really good at drawing, aren't you?
You're good.
It's amazing.
I think people who are looking at, say, the Mona Lisa or Mariko, they are really amazing paintings, aren't they?
No, no, not at all.
I am serious.
No, no, no, no, I understand serious.
I understand seriousness.
I understand, but it's the professionals who get the results.
Yes.
It's natural to work hard for the result.
Yes, that's right.
No, I don't even know if that's true.
And a little more, Mr. Tsubotsubo.
You are from Aichi Prefecture, aren't you?
Have you ever thought that you are a devil?
For example, when you're mean and happy.
Wow.
Do you ever feel like that?
Like when you give Mariko and the other members...
For example, when you put out a toy bug or something and they cackle?
Yuno Kokubou is a prankster.
She's a devil at heart.
He's naughty, and he's on the receiving end.
I see.
What kind of things does he do?
Kneecap.
A knee strike would be fine.
But a backward knee strike?
It just hurts.
I've had that happen to me.
My sister Menchan's Cocona...
She gets hit a lot.
What are you doing?
How did you come up with that?
He's the Devil of all Devils.
The King of Devils.
King of the Devils.
That's a great last name.
No one can stop him.
I see.
Is there any master in the house?
I've been beaten up. Pizza Pukko got hit by the King of Devlin once.
I've been attacked by the King of Devlin, too. It ended in an attempt, but I was like, "What the hell are you doing?
Did it end in an attempt? You've got to get to the bottom of this.
I mean, you came in halfway through, so I was like, "What are you doing?
I was like, "What the hell?
I'm a scary guy.
No one can really stop me.
I'll be careful.
By the way, what was that about?
You take pleasure in being mean to your partner.
I guess I'm the type that does that a lot.
I do that a lot.
I might be doing that a lot.
For example, I wonder what it is, so I do that quite a bit.
I wonder...
I don't know.
I often do some kind of surprise, like a surprise.
When I decide to shoot a video, I might do a surprise.
But even if I don't...
When it's not running at all.
If I'm late, I'll say I'm going to be late when I'm not running.
I might say I'm going to be late even though I'm not late, and I wonder how they are waiting for me, or I might do some kind of monitoring.
We do that kind of thing. We're pretty good at it.
I have a good sense.
I have a sense, so I notice.
I understand.
You have to take care of it.
He's got a good sense of urgency.
Yes, he is.
Preventive warfare is amazing.
Prevention.
But he's the type of guy who takes precautions.
I see.
The type that's totally impossible.
Well, well, well, well...
Let's see...
And also...
And this one too, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I guess this is it for now...
There were a lot of Ebichu-chan's here.
Rasha...
I don't know why they weren't in here.
I'm sorry.
There were so many of them!
Even in the comments, you know...
If Cocoon goes quiet, that's terrible.
That's for sure.
That would be the worst.
It says there are a lot of victims.
It says, "There are a lot of victims.
You know, we could start some kind of victims' group.
That sounds fun.
Against him.
I think the only way to curb him is to take legal action.
That's as far as I'll go.
I'm sure he'll calm down when he suddenly turns 20.
I may only be able to enjoy it for a couple more years.
Should we let him have his fun?
Rather...
It's when this doesn't stop.
Even when I'm 20.
I'm afraid of that, too.
That's amazing.
Soon
So this is how it is, isn't it?
Well, well, well, well, well, that's how it is.
Well then, if you have any more news, please continue to send them to us,
If you have any more letters, please send them to the plate.
So, the live broadcast is about to end... I'm kind of nervous!
On the contrary, it makes me nervous.
But cats are live, too, right?
Yes, we're doing a completely live broadcast for an hour and a half.
But I'm feeling a different kind of nervousness.
Here.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
I wonder what it's like to be in such a peaceful atmosphere.
It's so doggone fresh.
I was running on such a dogtooth.
Wow! You say, "Dogo, you dogo! You know what they say.
How do you call that? It's like an animal running away.
It's like when a wolf runs away.
I don't know. It wasn't that beautiful. - I want to hear it! I'd like to hear that.
But I started at events.
I also went to see him at some of his live performances and said hello to him.
So, rather than an impression, today was your very first impression.
That's right, it was just you, wasn't it?
Your mouth was so crooked.
It was the most crooked mouth I've ever seen.
I was so surprised.
I wonder if I'm being filmed.
I've never been high.
When we were meeting, my first thought was...
I was saying during the recording.
You have a sharp sense of humor.
I thought it was an interesting exchange with the master.
Sure, Sarpong also tsukkomi, but he's a tsukkomi machine, right?
Yes, he is.
He is a tsukkomi machine.
Every now and then, it becomes an annoying moment.
No, no, no, but it's amazing.
That's right. I'm a natural, after all, and my partner is a natural.
Oh, I see. I see.
I have to tease him.
That's right.
It's like you have to tease him.
I see.
By the way, in terms of Ebitu-chan, who's the lucky one? In terms of the members
We don't have a lucky comedian, but recently, Kaho...
I see...
Number 3 is a lucky guesser.
I see... I see...
Everyone else is a blabbermouth.
That's a lot of blokes.
What a disgusting group.
There's about nine of us.
It's when there's more than one blur that it becomes a real pain in the ass.
We've got a big traffic jam.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
I'm telling you, each one of them is so-so.
Okay, that's it.
Well, I think we're done with the live feed.
Oh, that's it?
That's it.
Next week?
Yes.
Next week at this time?
I'll see you next week.
Yes, please come back next week.
So thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.